The Princess Sapphire
Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano
The dreams I see are my secret
Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
Akai manto hira hira
A red cape fluttering
Uma o tobasu oujo
Galloping on a horse—the princess
Sore ga atashi
That’s me!
Lula dula lula dula
Lulu laa, lulaa
Ribon no kishi wa
The Princess Knight,
Honto wa hontto wa
Truly, truly,
Atashi nano sa
It’s really me!
Twenty-Fourth Episode
The Assassins
Before we get to
today's story,
let's briefly recall
the previous episodes.
The King disappeared
and it was decided that Sapphire
...would become the new King.
But on the day of the coronation
ceremony,
the Queen was deceived
by the evil Duralumin and Nylon..
...and she revealed that Sapphire
was a girl.
Therefore, Sapphire and the Queen were
locked in the coffin tower.
As a result, Duralumin felt
free to tyrannize the people.
Hearing of this,
Sapphire escaped...
...through the hole
that a little mouse showed her
And in the guise
of the phantom knight,
she defeated Duralumin's retinue
and saved the suffering prisoners.
Meanwhile, Duralumin was preparing
a cruel plan:
suspecting that the phantom
knight could be Sapphire,
he sent skilled assassins
to the tower.
Now, the life of Sapphire
and the Queen is in danger.
Let us now proceed to narrate
today's episode.
This damn mouse!
So, tell me: what is it?
Excuse me, cute little mouse,
but I really don't understand you.
But what is it you want to tell me?
Assassins?! Surely they
have come here to kill me!
Little mouse,
thank you for warning me!
- Mother, assassins are coming!
- What? Assassins?!
Absolutely do not open the door!
What do you want to do?
I want to get rid of the assassins!
Now, Gama, show us where the
room is of Sapphire and the Queen.
Come!
Sapphire...!
- They are in this room.
- Are you really sure they are here?
I locked them securely inside and
le ho mai lasciate uscire da qui,
except to make them work.
All right.
I don't like it very much.
They are just a girl and a woman.
Shut up and listen! After I have
made a hole in this door,
all you have to do is
throw the rocket bomb inside
- Okay!
- If the other three show up
kill them!
Do you understand? Now light it!
- Don't you think that's a bit much?
- Will you cut it out?!
Sapphire, hurry!
- The Phantom Knight!
- Hey, assassins!
What?! But how did you get in?
I can enter
from anywhere!
I will kill anyone who harms
the Queen and Sapphire!
And don't you dare ever again
get close to...
...the Queen
and Princess Sapphire!
It's strange...
That voice and that appearance.
It's as if I have
already known him.
Sapphire!
It's impossible..!
He looks a lot like her.
Yes, I've got it! It's almost impossible,
but he looks a lot like her!
Anyway, I must make sure of it.
I got scared! It's you, Gama!
Gama, it was terrible!
Many horrible men
tried to kill us.
But a man called
"phantom knight"...
..appeared and helped us
Listen, Gama, but who the hell is
the phantom knight?
So it's not her!
But she looks so much like her!
I can't waste time.
It must have been Duralumin
who sent those assassins.
I think he deserves a good lesson
and I'll make sure to give it to him!
The ghost knight!
Open the gate! I have something
to settle with Duralumin!
Open the gate!
Well, I never! Well, I never! Well, I
never! Well, I never! Well, I never!
Well, I never!
It happened that... It happened...
You see, it happened that...
But what the hell happened?
The ghost knight wants to
force his way into the castle!
What?! Idiot, don't let
him in! Drive him away!
Kill him!
Don't let him return alive!
Hey, Duralumin! I'm sending
your assassins back to you..
...that you sent
to the coffin tower!
Kill him!
Kill him immediately!
Grand Duke, what is going on?
Hey, you! Isn't it good?
One more!
Ole!
Listen, Duralumin!
The phantom knight..
...could appear
at any moment!
I will fight against you
until death!
I will soon annihilate you!
Prepare yourself for this! Come on!
- Hurrah! Hurrah!
- Long live the phantom knight!
Hey, you, innkeeper!
Bring more wine, quickly!
Listen, I will bring you
all the wine you want,
but then do you intend
to pay or not?
What? Do you want to force us to pay?
Yes, well... yes..
Damn you, try saying that again!
Do you know who we are or not?
- Help! Help!
- Innkeeper, bring us some wine
or we will have this child devoured
by King Plastic's dogs!
- Oh, forgive me!
- Bring some wine, now!
Damn you!
You will be torn apart by the dogs!
The phantom knight!
Soldiers of Duralumin, the phantom
knight will get you drunk!
Courage!
The phantom knight! How wonderful!
- The phantom knight!
- What happened to those people?
Because they sang
the song of the phantom knight,
they will become slaves!
The song of the phantom knight?
Yes, it's a popular song.
It goes like this:
"The phantom knight
is the champion"!
Wait! Wait!
Hooray! Hooray!
The phantom knight
is the champion!
Did you say he freed
the prisoners?
Yes, he's elusive! You can
never know when he will show up!
The Phantom Knight
is the champion!
- How wonderful!
- Idiot!
Curse that Phantom Knight...!
I've got it! I found a way to
capture the Phantom Knight!
The Phantom Knight
is very popular with children,
so, if we take a child
hostage, he will come to free him!
And we'll set a trap for him
that he will surely fall into!
The ghost knight
is the champion!
The ghost knight...
Help! Help!
- Taste it, it's a delicious juice.
- Thank you.
Ghost knight!
Cursed ghost knight,
this time you will die!
- Help!
- Mama! Mama!
Help, I'm scared!
Cry! Cry! The ghost
knight will come to help you!
And if he comes, we will win!
If he comes to this square,
the cannon, the rockets and the arrows
will attack him!
He will die in an instant!
But what is he waiting for?
- Mom!
- Help!
What's happening, ghost
knight? Are you scared?
Damned ghost knight!
I wonder if he's scared.
Cry, children! Cry!
And the knight...
Is coming from the sky?!
Who's next!
Water! Throw some water!
But not on me, you idiot!
What?!
I'm dying of rage!
And now go back
all of you home.
- Thank you, ghost knight!
- Be careful!
Don't get kidnapped again!
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
- You are Baron Nylon, aren't you?
- Shut up!
Good heavens! Don't you want
to know where the ghost knight is?
The ghost knight...
What?
Ah, how beautiful you are.
You are looking for the
ghost knight, aren't you?
Yes! I wonder where that
damned knight is, damn it!
- I know!
- What? Really?
Tell me, please! Please,
beautiful lady! Please!
I will tell the Grand Duke
Duralumin! I would be truly glad...
...to see that clean-shaven
face of Grand Duke Duralumin.
Yes, but don't you prefer to see mine?
No! I prefer the clean-shaven
one of Duralumin!
I see... Then I will take
you to the castle, alright.
Here, please have the
courtesy to wait here, please!
Soon Grand Duke
Duralumin will arrive.
Yes, of course, I'll wait!
How beautiful and kind you are,
damn it!
Well, then wait here
just a moment.
Is that the lady who knows
where the ghost knight is?
Yes, sir.
Then tell me:
where is the ghost knight?
Where is he? Where is the phantom knight?
I want to see him because he is very
handsome! I want to see him because he is...
So, where is the phantom
knight? Answer me!
And show me your face!
He's here!
The phantom knight is here!
- How handsome he is!
- The phantom knight!
- Quick, someone catch him!
- Don't move!
I promised you that I
would appear in the castle!
I kept my promise!
Here I am!
Don't move!
I'll take this!
Catch him!
Take back the crown!
This stupid, foolish, imbecile!
You brought the phantom
knight right into my house!
I am furious!
Sapphire, you are running
very late today.
Gama is coming!
- Hey, open up!
- Please, wait!
Wait?! It's time for Sapphire to
go get the water! Understood?
Wait a moment, please!
Wait!
I can't wait!
She's not here! In fact, I thought
the phantom knight was Sapphire!
- That's not true!
- Yes, exactly!
Listen, do you know what will happen to you
if Sapphire escapes from the castle?
What happens is that you will be hanged!
I warned you!
And now prepare yourself for this!
No! I...
I am sure that Sapphire
went to fetch water.
Don't lie!
Fine, I will go see!
But if she isn't there,
you will be hanged!
Sapphire,
we are finally at the end!
Soon we will see the sun...
Hey! Where have you been?
Since Gama forgot
to close the door,
I went out onto the skylight
to play with the mice.
But I started fetching
water at the right time.
Shut up! You can't do
whatever you want!
Don't laugh!
Yet there is something strange.
I feel as if I've been tricked
Damn phantom knight!
How clever! Brave!
Wonderful! Damn it!
Can't I even kill
a single girl?
Even the assassins
were sent back!
And that knight was not
caught in our trap!
Now I've got it!
I've got an idea!
I'm fed up with your stupid ideas!
Don't bother me!
No, no! But this one is really good!
This is the best!
Fortunately,
there's a storm outside!
I can't miss
this opportunity!
You'd better tell Gama
to kill them in secret,
rather than sending assassins.
"Gama, today is the day
most favorable.
Kill the Queen and Sapphire
tonight.
You will receive the reward
from my emissary. Baron Nylon".
And try to do it well!
Honestly, it wouldn't be my
intention to kill a girl,
but I can't help it
- Gama!
- Sapphire!
May I know
where you are going at this hour?
I... well... I...
Nowhere!
You were looking for some hole
to escape through, right?
Alright! If you really want to get out,
you can do it now!
But you won't make it out alive! Got it?
Gama! What do you want to do?!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo
Even if devils come, even if storms arrive,
tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai
Our bonded hearts will never part.
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa
Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP